...from a sex swing. Heh.
(Raj:)This may have been a mistake.
(Howard:)Relax, everything's gonna be fine.
(Howard:)Before I met Bernadette,
I was in here every other day.
Little tip, turn off your "I Like Big
Butts" ringtone before you go in.
(Raj:)- This is all your fault.
- How is this my fault?
(Raj:)If you weren't screwing around
with Sheldon's assistant...
- ...this wouldn't have happened.
- I wasn't screwing around.
(Raj:)Oh, of course not, she was just
sniffing around your goods...
(Raj:)...because she was hunting for truffles.
(HR Woman:)Ah. Mr. Wolowitz, it's been a while.
Hey, Janine. Heh. How're Tom and the kids?
(Penny:)Fine.
You must be Dr. Hofstadter?
(Leonard:)Yes, but I think this is all
a big misunderstanding.
(Raj:)Yeah, me too. I didn't do anything.
(Janine:)Is that alcohol on your breath?
(Raj:)Howard built a sex robot.
(Howard:)That is not true.
All I did was build a robot.